bottr.me 2017-09-01

# Privacy Policy

Last updated: 19/08/2016 

We at HELP Inc. (the “Company”, “we”, or “us”) are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy entails the way in which your Personal Information or Usage Information will be collected, used, shared, stored, protected or disclosed by us. This Privacy Policy applies to the mobile application or website developed by us in relation to services provided to you by the Company from time to time (“Services”). By using our Services, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of the Privacy Policy, you are directed to discontinue accessing/using our application in any way. We strongly recommend that you read the policy carefully before proceeding with any transaction on our application. 

**1\. What Information we collect?**

  * a. Personal Information

We collect information about you including but not limited to the following:

    1. For procuring services from the professionals registered on our platform (“End-users” or “Customers”):  
Name, e-mail id, profile password, phone number. 
    2. For providing your expertise as professional services to the end users/customers (“Service Provider/s”);

Name, e-mail id, profile password, phone number and bank account details for remitting the amount received from the Customers and/or Service Providers and in addition to the above information collected might also comprise of account holder’s name, account number, account type, branch address, branch phone number, routing number, swift code and any other relevant information for the purpose of the Service.. If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand that some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. 

  * b. Information We Collect As You Access And Use Our Service (“Usage Information”):

When you visit or use our Services, we collect information about your computer or mobile device. Some of the information we collect include:

    1. Computer IP addresses mobile device ids (the unique identifier assigned to a device by a manufacturer), technical information about your computer or mobile device (such as type of device, web browser or operating system).
    2. Your mobile device’s geographic location (specific geographic location if you’ve enabled collection of that information, or general geographic location automatically).
    3. Cookies: If you are accessing our mobile application through computers we place “Cookies” on your computer to identify it. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features. If you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. You hereby agree that this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

No other information which is provided by you while accessing the Service is stored or used by us, unless otherwise required by the applicable law.

  * c. Information third parties provide about you:

We may also collect and store the information provided by others about you. For example: a review by a customer for your services provided on our application. Such information provided by a customer can be combined with the information we have to enhance our ability to serve you.

**2\. Why we collect your information?**

We collect information about you for the following general purposes: For registration and to manage your account, including to facilitate your access to and use of our Services; to communicate with you in general, including to provide information about us; to enable us to publish your reviews, forum posts, and other content; to respond to your questions and comments, to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and to enforce our Terms of Use. 

**3\. With whom we share your information?**

We neither rent nor sell your Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. However, we do share your Personal Information with third parties as described below: 

  * **Third-party vendors:** We employ third party vendors to provide Services on our behalf for varied purposes like business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution etc. We may authorize such vendors to collect information on our behalf in order to operate features of our application or to deliver services tailored to your needs. We assure that such information used by third party vendors is only to perform their functions and they are not permitted to share or use that information for any other purpose.
  * **Companies within our corporate family:** We may be required to provide information about you to our parent or subsidiary company or corporate affiliates. To the extent our parent company or subsidiaries or corporate affiliates have information about you, they will follow the best practices as described in this Privacy Policy when using it.
  * **Business Partners:** We take the help of our Business Partners in conjunction with whom we offer our Services to you. If you choose to access these optional services provided by our Business Partners, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those Partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party Business Partners.
  * **User Profiles and Submissions:** Certain user profile information, including without limitation a user’s name, location, and any video or image content that such user has uploaded to the Services, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services or address your request for Company’s services. Your account privacy settings allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Services and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Again, we do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service which may interact with our Services.
  * **Affiliated Websites:** If you were referred to us from another website, we may have to share information pertaining to registration information including but not limited to name, e mail address, phone numbers etc. In such instances we encourage you to read and review their Privacy Policy of the website that referred you to us. We will not be responsible for the handling of such information by them.
  * **Business Transfers:** We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.
  * **Government Bodies:** We may disclose your Personal Information and Usage Information as and when required in response to a sub-poena, court order, government demand or to comply with any legal requirements for protecting our interest. We will contact you by e-mail when we have to adhere to such legal request. All communications sent by us at such email address shall be deemed to have been communicated to you.

**4\. How do we protect your information?**

We want you to have full faith in having your information safe and secure with us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Information and Usage Information submitted to us. While no Services can guarantee full-proof security, we have appropriate administrative, technical and security procedures to keep your information intact, secure and confidential. Your information is handled only for the purposes required by authorized employees or agents or third party vendors and the like and we employ appropriate firewalls, encryption technologies and intrusion detection systems to keep your information secure and safe from any unauthorized use. 

**5\. How can you change your information and what happens when you cancel or close your account?**

You can anytime ask us to amend the information provided by you by contacting us at [hello@bottr.me](mailto:hello@bottr.me). We will make changes to the information provided by you as soon as reasonably practicable. If you wish to cancel your account you should contact us at [hello@bottr.me](mailto:hello@bottr.me). However, you should take note that if even after the suspension of your account we will retain your Personal Information and Usage Information for complying with certain regulatory or legal obligations, resolving disputes, preventing fraud, enforcing agreements or for any other business reasons. 

**6\. What about the safety of children?**

Our Services are directed to serve a very general audience. We reserve a right of use of our Services to persons above 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13. If we discover that a person below 13 years of age or younger has provided Personal Information to us, we automatically delete such information. If you are a parent or guardian of a minor under the age of thirteen (13) and believe he or she has disclosed Personal Information to us, please contact us at [hello@bottr.me](mailto:hello@bottr.me). 

**7\. What happens when you use our Services from outside the United States?**

If you are accessing our application from outside the United States, please be mindful that such information may be transferred, stored or processed in the United States where our servers or central databases are located. Even though you access it from a foreign land we ensure we will follow the best practices in keeping your information protected. By using our Services you understand that we are governed by the United States Privacy and Data Protection Laws which are very different from the laws of your country. 

**8\. How does a change in our Privacy Policy affect you?**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you (for example, by email or a sign-in notification or some other means). By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy; if you do not agree to the change, simply don’t use the Service after the change is effective, in which case the change will not apply to you. 

**9\. How can you contact us?**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us at [hello@bottr.me](mailto:hello@bottr.me).
